<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bidhya N Yadav</title>
    <link>https://bidhya.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bidhya N Yadav</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bidhya.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GPU_for_tensorflow</title>
      <link>https://bidhya.github.io/post/gpu_tf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bidhya.github.io/post/gpu_tf/</guid>
      <description>GPU installation on Windows 10 for Tensorflow Even though installation of Tensorflow is more streamlined (even on Windows), there are still few nuances on uisng GPU. Here are the steps to using GPU with tensorflow.
Refere to this page for specific GPU version of sofware/driver
Important : Make sure to download the exact version specified on google site. Since, there is rapid updates to both tensorflow and nvidia downloading the latest NVIDIA drivers will not work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conda Enviornment Setup </title>
      <link>https://bidhya.github.io/post/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 14:38:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bidhya.github.io/post/second-post/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my workflow for working in Python across platforms (Windows, Linux, and HPC clusters)
 Install miniconda (Anaconda will do as well, but perhaps don&amp;rsquo;t follow this workflow with Anaconda) conda config &amp;ndash;add channels conda-forge #to make conda-forge default conda env update -f bidhya_environment.yaml #update everything from the yaml file conda update &amp;ndash;all #I run it periodically to update everything to latest version; but new things break more often so take care  Sample Conda_env.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://bidhya.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 14:18:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bidhya.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Starting with hugo blogging
More about me later</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github user page using Hugo on Windows</title>
      <link>https://bidhya.github.io/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 14:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bidhya.github.io/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Since most of the online instruction for Hugo was related to Mac/Linux, I decided to write post for my own sanity!
Change1
  Download Hugo executable from this site
 Unzip and put on any folder Set path to to this exe file so that you can start using hugo command from any folder location    Create Hugo Project
 hugo new site blog cd blog git submodule add https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>